(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-28T21:35:31.183188",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場の方へ マスクの着用にご協力ください
[Attention: Please wear a mask]
携帯電話の電源はお切りならずマナーモードに設定をお願いいたします。
Please set phones to manner mode (do not power off).
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます。
Photography, audio, and video recording are prohibited.
#わためソロライブ SNSでの感想・スクショ投稿OK 開演までしばらくお待ち下さい
#WatameSoloLive: SNS posts & screenshots OK! Please wait.
Flower Stands フラワースタンド紹介
[Flower Stands]
単品販売グッズ 1
[Official Merchandise - Part 1]
単品販売グッズ 2
[Official Merchandise - Part 2]
単品販売グッズ 3
[Official Merchandise - Part 3]
Attention ご来場の方へ マスクの着用にご協力ください
[Attention: Please wear a mask]
携帯電話の電源はお切りならずマナーモードに設定をお願いいたします。
Please set phones to manner mode (do not power off).
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます。
Photography, audio, and video recording are prohibited.
#わためソロライブ SNSでの感想・スクショ投稿OK 開演までしばらくお待ち下さい
#WatameSoloLive: SNS posts & screenshots OK! Please wait.
Flower Stands フラワースタンド紹介
[Flower Stands]
単品販売グッズ 1
[Official Merchandise - Part 1]
単品販売グッズ 2
[Official Merchandise - Part 2]
単品販売グッズ 3
[Official Merchandise - Part 3]
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションがヴァイスシュヴァルツに参戦！
Hololive Production joins Weiss Schwarz!
トライアルデッキ＋ ホロライブプロダクション好評発売中！
Trial Deck + Hololive Production is now on sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
D4DJ Groovy Mix！
D4DJ Groovy Mix!
ホロライブ楽曲コラボ開催だよ！ぞくぞくといろんな楽曲を実装しちゃうんだって！
Hololive song collaboration is happening! They're adding a bunch of songs one after another!
ゲームBGMやインスト、カバー楽曲もDJ気分で遊べちゃう！
You can play game BGMs, instrumentals, and cover songs with DJ vibes!
つながろ、グルミクで！
Let's connect with Groovy Mix!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz doesn't stop even with the Hololive Production booster pack!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション好評発売中！
Booster Pack Hololive Production is now on sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
本日は
Today,
角巻わためファーストライブ「わためぇ Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo」サポートドロードにご来場いただきまして、誠に
thanks to all the wonderful flower stands provided by Bushiroad for Tsunomaki Watame's 1st Live "Watame Night Fever!!" in Zepp Tokyo,
ありがとうございます！
thank you so much!
記念すべき角巻わためファーストソロライブを楽しみにしてくださっているわためいとの皆さん、本日はどうぞよろしくお願いいたします！
We hope you all enjoy Tsunomaki Watame's long-awaited 1st solo live!
さて、公演を最後まで楽しんでいただくために、皆さまへいくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
Now then, to ensure everyone enjoys the concert all the way to the end,
させていただきます。
we have a few announcements for you.
まず初めに、会場のロビー、客席内ではマスクの着用が必須となります。
First, wearing a mask is mandatory inside the lobby and guest seating areas.
公演中の掛け声などは、新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点からご遠慮ください。
To prevent COVID-19 infection, please refrain from cheering or shouting loudly during the performance.
ぜひさっきみたいなね、拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いします。
We kindly ask for your support through applause and penlights, as mentioned earlier!
また、会場内では立って応援していただいても問題ございませんが、周りのお客さまにご迷惑にならないようご配慮お願いいたします。
Also, while standing to cheer inside the venue is permitted, please be considerate and avoid causing any inconvenience to surrounding guests.
会場内ではスタッフの方の指示に従ってください。
Please follow the staff's instructions at all times inside the venue.
客席内では周りのお客さまに迷惑をかけるような危険行為はご遠慮ください。会場内では携帯電話、スマートフォンをマナーモードにしていただきますようお願いいたします。
And please ensure cell phones and smartphones are kept in manner mode while inside the venue.
本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入るため、客席の
Since video recording and photography equipment will be operating inside the venue during the performance,
お客さまの様子がわためとみんなの様子が映り込む場合がございます。
there may be times when audience members and Watame appear on camera.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションや今後の活動に使用する可能性がありますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
Please understand in advance that this footage and these photos may be used for promotions and future activities.
いいよね？
Sound good?
Sound good!
いいってことだよね？
That means yes!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
公演中ライブの様子を撮影することは演出の都合上禁止とさせていただきます。
Please note that photographing the live performance itself is prohibited for production reasons.
ペンライトは周りのお客さまのご迷惑にならないようご配慮をお願いします。頭の上にだしたり、大きく左右に振り回されますと、後ろのお客さまや周りのお客さまのご迷惑となる場合がございます。
Again, please be careful not to hold penlights too high or wave them wildly so as not to disturb those around you.
スタッフさんが注意させていただく場合がございますのでご容赦ください。
Please understand that staff may need to caution you if this happens.
以上のことが守られない場合いないと思うんだけど、安全確保のため公演を一時中断もしくは中止させていただくこともございます。
In the event these rules cannot be followed, we may temporarily suspend or even cancel the performance to ensure everyone's safety.
最後にご気分の優れない場合など、何かございましたらお早めにお近くのスタッフにお申し付けください。
Lastly, if you are feeling unwell, please notify a nearby staff member right away.
また、地震などの緊急時にはスタッフが誘導いたします。
In case of emergencies like earthquakes, please follow staff guidance.
スタッフの指示があるまでお。
Please follow staff instructions until—
あっ、間違えたね！お席にて応援ありがとう！お席にてお待ちください。
Oops, I messed up! Please wait in your seats, and thank you for your support!
続いて、配信でご覧のわためいとのみんなへの注意点をお伝えします。
Next, important notices for everyone watching the stream:
本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
Recording, filming, mirror broadcasting, or unauthorized uploading of this live stream is strictly prohibited.
スクリーンショットを撮影して画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です！
Taking screenshots and posting them with images on social media is very welcome!
ぜひお願いします！
Please do!
本公演のハッシュタグは#わためソロライブです。
The official hashtag for today's concert is #わためソロライブ.
ぜひハッシュタグを使ってライブを一緒に盛り上げてください。
Please use the hashtag to hype up the live together!
また、ライブ配信についてデータの通信量が多くなることが想定されるため、スマートフォンでご覧になる場合にはWi-Fiでのご利用を推奨いたします。インターネット回線の接続が不安定な場合は配信動画のクオリティを保証できません。
Also, since network traffic for the livestream may be high, we recommend using Wi-Fi if you are watching on a smartphone, as unstable internet connections can affect stream quality.
万全の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、生配信の特性上、不慮の障害で映像の乱れや一時停止等が発生する可能性が御座います。あらかじめご了解ください。
We are preparing as best as we can to deliver a great live stream, but due to the nature of live streaming, unforeseen technical difficulties may cause stream disruptions or temporary freezes, so we appreciate your understanding.
さて、わためからのご案内は、私からのご案内は以上となります。
Well, that's all the announcements from me!
開演まであと少し。私はステージに出る準備をしてきます！
We're almost ready to open! I'll go get ready to take the stage!
それでは開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait just a moment until the performance begins.
本日は角巻わためファーストライブ『わためナイトフィーバー!! in Zepp Tokyo』supported by ブシロードにご来場いただきまして誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending Tsunomaki Watame 1st Live "Watame Night Fever!! in Zepp Tokyo" supported by Bushiroad today.
大変長らくお待たせいたしました！
Thank you so much for waiting!
本公演はまもなく開演いたします。
This performance will begin shortly.
会場の皆さんも配信でご覧の皆さんも一緒に盛り上がる準備はできていますか？
Are you all ready to get hyped together, whether you're here at the venue or watching via stream?
いいですね！
That's great!
最後まで一緒に楽しみましょう！
Let's enjoy it together until the very end!
わためナイトフィーバー！スタート！
Watame Night Fever! Start!
...
おはよう 今日 が はじまる
Good morning, today is beginning.
どんな 1 日 を 描こう か な
What kind of day shall I sketch out?
ワクワク お絵描き 夢物語 綴ろう
Exciting drawings, dreaming stories, let's write them down.
そんな 子ども じゃ いられない よ
You can't stay a child like that anymore.
分かっ た ふり し た 大人 の 自分 が 言う
Says my adult self who pretends to understand.
笑い ながら 嫌 な 事 話し たり
Laughing while talking about unpleasant things,
泣き ながら ゲーム を し て たり
Crying while playing video games,
思いがけない こと の その 全部 が
All those unexpected things—
君 の せい 、 本当 に ありがとう
It's all thanks to you, thank you so much.
おはようって おはようって 今日もまた言えるね
Saying "good morning" again today as well.
君と君と重ねた色が増える
The colors layered with you and me increase.
難しいことは分からない
I don't understand difficult things,
無邪気な笑顔に助かる
I'm saved by your innocent smile.
何度でも君を見送るよ
I'll see you off no matter how many times.
せーの！で駆け出したあの日から
Ever since that day we dashed out on the count of three!
ずいぶん遠くへやっとここまで来たけど
We've come so far, finally making it this far.
ねぇ 今 君 が 見てる 私 は
Hey, the me you are looking at right now—
どんな 顔 し てる ？ ちゃんと 笑え て る の か な
What face is she making? Are you smiling properly?
誰 も 知ら ない がんばり が あっ た ね
There were efforts nobody knew about, right?
君 も 私 も そう 、 だから 何度 も 言う ありがとう
Both you and me, so I'll say it over and over: thank you.
おかえりって ただいま って 今日 も まだ 言える よ
Saying "welcome back" and "I'm home" again today.
君と君と重ねた色が増える
The colors layered with you and me increase.
白く て 柔らかい 夜 に
In the white and soft night,
泣き出す 声 は 震え て も
Even if the crying voice trembles,
何度でも朝を迎えた
We welcomed the morning countless times.
おかえりって ただいまって 今日もまだ言えるよ
Saying "welcome back" and "I'm home" again today.
君と君と重ねた色が増える
The colors layered with you and me increase.
白くて柔らかい夜に 泣き出す声は震えても
In the white and soft night, even if the crying voice trembles,
なんとでも朝を迎えた
We welcomed the morning countless times.
いつだってそう「僕なんて」さっそて
Always thinking, "A nobody like me..."
俯いてばかりのMayday
Another Mayday spent looking down.
遠くたっていい ほら 虹をまたいで
It's okay if it's far, just step right over the rainbow.
さあ 心のままに音を奏でる
Now, play your music straight from the heart.
響け 僕らの想いを乗せて
Resound, carrying all of our feelings with it.
高く遠く 歌を紡いで la la la
Weaving a song high and far, la la la...
新しい明日を恐れない
I'm not afraid of a brand new tomorrow.
無邪気な笑顔に救われ また帰る場所があるから
Saved by your innocent smile, there's a place to return to.
何度でも君を思い出すよ
No matter how many times, I'll remember you.
心の中の音を聴かせて
Let me hear the music inside my heart.
大袈裟でいいの ありのままの自分で
It's fine if it's over-the-top, just be your true self.
咲き誇れもっと いつまでもずーっと
Blossom even more proudly, ever and ever onward.
歌いながら日々を紡いで
Weaving through the days while singing along.
ああ またやっちゃった
Ah, I messed up again.
隠してたわけじゃないのかも
Maybe I wasn't trying to hide it after all?
きっとただ言ってないだけ
I just definitely haven't said it yet.
だって恥ずかしいんだもん
Because it's so embarrassing!
意外と寂しんぼ
Surprisingly lonely,
意外と甘えんぼ
surprisingly clingy,
意外と慌てんぼ
surprisingly flustered,
意外と照れ屋
surprisingly shy.
丸い飛行機雲
A round contrail,
飛び出したカップケーキ
a cupcake that popped out,
三回目コンディショナー
conditioner for the third time,
余るパズル
and leftover puzzle pieces.
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢見心地
Floating softly in a dreamlike haze,
ひとつひとつ数えておやすみなさい
counting them one by one, good night.
密かに芽生えたこのキモチ
This feeling that quietly sprouted—
まっすぐ見つめないで
don't stare at me straight on.
「なんだだったっけ…///」
"What was that again...?"
言葉にしちゃうときっとそうじゃない
When I put it into words, it's surely not quite right;
テレちゃうだけおちゃらけちゃうじゃない
I just get shy and act all silly.
本当の本当は隠したいんじゃないの
The truth is, I don't really want to hide it—
もうそうじゃないのにさあ
even though it's already not like that anymore!
曖昧なんじゃない このキモチは間違いじゃない
It's not ambiguous; this feeling is no mistake.
指切りげんまん かなりドジっ子で
Pinky swear, I'm quite a clumsy girl,
優柔不断でも 絶対に毎日
and even if I'm indecisive, without fail, every single day
会いに来てくれるよね？
you'll come see me, right?
本来臆病で
Naturally timid
案外泣き虫
and surprisingly a crybaby,
全然変わらずに
completely unchanged,
元来君ばっか！
it's always been all about you!
当たり前のようにキュンにしちゃう
Making my heart flutter so naturally,
君がいないとガッカリしちゃう
feeling so let down when you're not around,
本当の本当にショボリしちゃうわ
feeling genuinely down in the dumps,
会いたくなっちゃうなあ
wanting to see you so badly.
後悔ばっかりしちゃう
Always full of regrets,
この心も勇気出しちゃえ
let's muster up the courage in this heart too!
この指とまれ
Put your finger here.
弱いところ気付かれたり 寂しさごと包まれたり
Having my weak spots noticed, being wrapped up in loneliness,
いつまでも笑い合ったり たまれにはムッといさかいをしたり
laughing together forever, sometimes getting a little cross and bickering—
ずっとずっと傍にいてほしい…約束だぞ
I want you right by my side forever... that's a promise!
「いっちまった///」
("I went and said it///")
もしかしたら運命かも
Maybe it's destiny,
赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
maybe I can see the red thread.
本当の本当はバレてんのかも
The truth is, maybe you've already figured it out,
目合わせらんないかも
maybe I can't even look you in the eyes.
曖昧なんじゃない
It's not ambiguous at all;
たくさん私を見てて 指さした！
look at me a whole lot—I pointed right at you!
当たり前のようにキュンにしちゃう
Making my heart flutter so naturally,
君がいないとガッカリしちゃう
feeling so let down when you're not around,
本当の本当にショボリしちゃうわ
feeling genuinely down in the dumps,
会いたくなっちゃうなあ
wanting to see you so badly.
後悔ばっかりしちゃう
Always full of regrets,
この心も勇気出しちゃえ
let's muster up the courage in this heart too!
この指とまれ
Put your finger here.
みんな！いっせーので見上げてみて！
Everyone! On three, look up at the sky!
どんな大きな季節だって
No matter how grand the season,
嬉しいね！ ドキドキドキドキドキ
I'm so happy! My heart is pounding so fast!
楽しいね！ 最高の一日にするから
So much fun! I'm gonna make this the best day ever,
最後まで一緒にいようね！
so let's stick together right to the very end!
弱いところ気付かれたり
Having my weak spots noticed,
寂しさごと包まれたり
being wrapped up in loneliness,
いつまでも笑い合ったり
laughing together forever,
たまれにはムッといさかいをしたり
sometimes getting a little cross and bickering—
ずっとずっと傍にいてほしい…約束だぞ
I want you right by my side forever... that's a promise!
もしかしたら運命かも
Maybe it's destiny,
赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
maybe I can see the red thread.
本当の本当はバレてんのかも
The truth is, maybe you've already figured it out,
目合わせらんないかも
maybe I can't even look you in the eyes.
曖昧なんじゃない
It's not ambiguous at all;
たくさん私を見てて 指さした！
look at me a whole lot—I pointed right at you!
指切りげんまん
Pinky swear,
かなり頑固で
quite stubborn,
優柔不断でも
even if indecisive,
絶対に毎日
without fail every day
会いに来てくれるよね？
you'll come see me, right?
本来臆病で
Naturally timid
案外泣き虫
and surprisingly a crybaby,
全然変わらずに
completely unchanged,
元来君ばっか！
it's always been all about you!
ずっとずっと大好きだよ
I love you so, so much.
la la la...
あぁ、またやっちゃった 隠してたわけじゃないの
Ah, I did it again... It's not like I was hiding it.
きっとただ言ってないだけ だって恥ずかしいんだもん
I just haven't said it yet, because it's embarrassing.
意外と寂しんぼ 意外と甘えんぼ
Surprisingly lonely, surprisingly clingy,
意外と慌てんぼ 意外と照れ屋
surprisingly flustered, surprisingly shy.
ずっとずっと傍にいて欲しい
I want you to stay right by my side forever.
…約束だぞっ
...It's a promise, okay?
言っちゃった///
I said it ///
もしかしたら運命かも 赤い糸が見えちゃうかも
Maybe it's destiny, maybe I can see the red string.
本当の本当はバレてるのかも
Truth be told, maybe you've figured it out.
目合わせらんないかも
Maybe I can't even look you in the eyes.
曖昧なんてない たくさん私を見てて
There's nothing ambiguous, look at me plenty!
指切った！
Pinky swear!
mayday, mayday
mayday, can you read me? i'm in distress
my heart's accelerating from the raging pain in my chest
baby, i can't get you out of my mind, cuz your allure has got me head over heels
i think i'm going crazy
mayday, darling i just can't get enough
it's out of character for me to stop when i'm so in love
hey, hey, come on, and excite me again
dead set on diving right inside of your heart, you gotta let me in
あぁ見え透いた甘い罠 あぁハマってあげるから
Ah, a transparent sweet trap, ah, because I'll fall for it
あぁ自在にコントロール していたはずなのに
Ah, even though I should have been controlling it freely
クラクラって酔っちゃいそうなくらい 甘い匂い誘われ
Lured by a sweet scent that makes me dizzy
フラフラって寄っちゃいそうわ あぁもう help me...
Faltering and wandering over, ah, help me...
mayday, everything's so outta control
emotions spinning out and caving in, an unending roller coaster
ladies always staying inside of the lines?
i can't pretend i'm anything of the like
how can i not be naughty?
no way, not a chance you're getting with me
my misunderstanding, there's no guarantee
like a lifeless puppet until you got the strings, i'll come alive and dance whenever you ask me
だってもう溶けだそうような体温に魅わされ
Because I'm enchanted by a body temperature that feels like it's melting
なんか変 あたしじゃないみたい あぁもう rescue me...
Something's strange, I'm not myself, ah, rescue me...
嫌々って漏れちゃうくらいにあたしを困らせて 何もかもあたしからは絶対… rescue meして
Tease me enough to let out reluctant sighs, absolutely... rescue me from everything
ねぇどうして愛は悪戯するんだろう ねぇいつかはこの痛みも消えるの
Hey, why does love play tricks? Hey, will this pain disappear one day?
本来は案外簡単に否定して壊れちゃうけど傷だらけの心は…
Originally it's quite easily denied and broken, but a heart full of scars...
気付けば手を伸ばしちゃってその遠さ苦しくて
Before I knew it, I reached out, and that distance is painful
キミも手を伸ばしてくれたら…
If you would reach out your hand too...
イタイここにいたい のcry 落とし込む場所その手で触れてほら mayday
It hurts, I want to be here, cry, a place to settle, touch with your hand, look, mayday
クラクラって酔っちゃいそうなくらい甘い匂い誘われ フラフラって寄っちゃいそうわ あぁもう save me...
Lured by a sweet scent that makes me dizzy, faltering and wandering over, ah, save me...
help me rescue me save me mayday
だってもう溶けだそうような体温に魅わされ きっとそう溢れ出しちゃうんだもう… rescue meして
Because I'm enchanted by a body temperature that feels like it's melting, surely overflowing... rescue me
ねえ、どうして 愛はいたずらするんだろう ねえ、いつかはこの痛みも消えるの
Hey, why does love play tricks? Hey, will this pain disappear one day?
ねえ、いつかは この痛みも消えるの…
Hey, will this pain disappear one day...
本来は案外簡単に期待して壊れちゃうけど
Originally it's quite easily expected and broken, but
臆病な手を心は… 気付けば手を伸ばしてくれたなら…
A timid hand, the heart... If you reached out your hand before I knew it...
痛い、ここにいたいのcry
It hurts, I want to be here, cry
落ち着く場所、その手で触れてよ、ほらmayday
A place to settle, touch it with your hand, look, mayday
クラクラって酔っちゃいそうなまいにちを過され
Spending days that make me feel dizzy
フラフラって寄っちゃてちょわ あぁもう save me...
Faltering and wandering over, ah, save me...
help me
save me, save me, save me, save me, save me... rescue me
ダメダメよ☆
No no no!
君は招き寄せてさ あふれ出したがる
You draw me in, overflowing—
モーレツぅ
Fiercely!
あふれ出したがる モーレツぅ
Overflowing fiercely!
して...
And...
はぁ…
Hah...
こんばんはー！どうもどうも！
Good evening! Hello, hello!
ちょっと水飲んでもいいかな？
Can I drink some water?
こんばんはどうぞだ
Good evening, go right ahead.
じゃあ水飲みますね
Well then, I'll drink some water.
水ってうめぇな
Water is so good.
謎の拍手
Mysterious applause.
水ってうめぇねぇ！
Water is so good!
水ってうめぇよなぁ！
Water tastes amazing, right!
なんだろうね
I wonder what it is.
つどいまっき…わためファーストライブ！
Tsunomaki Watame 1st Live!
わためナイトフィーバー in ゼッポン東京！いよいよ始まったぞー！
Watame Night Fever in Zepp Tokyo! It's finally started!
みんな、見に来てくれて本当にありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much for coming!
ついにわため初の単独ソロライブ
Finally, my very first solo live.
みんな楽しみにしてたよな、な？
You were all looking forward to it, right?
配信見てくれてる人も楽しみにしてたよね、な？
Those watching the stream too, right?
今日はね、ハッシュタグ「#わためソロライブ」で
Today, please tweet with the hashtag
つぶやいて欲しいんだよね。いいかな？
"#WatameSoloLive". Is that okay?
でも見るのに夢中か、みんな。
But everyone's too absorbed in watching!
ねえ、わための魅力にやられてんじゃないのか？
Hey, are you captivated by my charm?
やめとこうか、調子乗るの、あれ、やめとこうね。
Shall I stop getting carried away? Let's stop.
え、調子乗ってもいいってことなのかな？
Uh, does that mean it's okay to get carried away?
変な動きやめとこうね。せっかくのソロライブなのにね
Let's stop weird movements on my special solo live.
「#わためソロライブ」でたくさんつぶやいて欲しいな
I hope you'll tweet a lot with #WatameSoloLive.
現地に来てくれてるみんなとも遊びたいけど、ペンライト持ってますか？
I want to play with everyone here, but do you have penlights?
お？何色？みんな、黄色だね！すごい！
Oh? What color? Everyone, it's yellow! Amazing!
わためカラーなんだね！ペンライト、フリフリフリ！
It's Watame color! Penlights, shake shake shake!
見えてるよ！うちわ持ってくれてる人も、ありがとうね！
I can see you! To those holding uchiwa fans, thanks!
せっかくだから見ちゃおうかな？
Since we're at it, should I take a look?
見えてるよ！最前の人さ、首痛くない？
I can see you! To the person in front, doesn't your neck hurt?
わためもね、みんなのお席の方に行ってね
When I went to everyone's seats during rehearsal,
前の方で首痛いよね、イケメンのポーズみたいになっちゃうね。
towards the front your neck hurts like a handsome pose.
声出せないの辛いね、受けてるのかわかんないよ。
Not being able to use your voice is tough, is it landing?
滑ってないかな？大丈夫かな？
Did I bomb? Will it be okay?
受けてる受けてる！拍手してもらえると安心する、ありがとう！
It's landing! Applause brings peace of mind, thank you!
ステップとかダメみたいなんだけど、上半身なら動かしていいらしいから
Steps aren't allowed, but upper body movement is fine,
上半身でわためへの愛を伝えてもらってもいいか、恥ずかしい？
so can you express your love with your upper body? Embarrassed?
なんかこういうのとかさ、あ、やってくれてる！
Like doing things like this, ah, you're doing it!
いいね！ファリータス、いいね！
Nice! Fanitas, nice!
さすがわためナイトフィーバー、毎週踊ってるだけあるね！
As expected of Watame Night Fever, dancing every week pays off!
いや、こうやって欲しかったんだ、ありがとうね！
No, I wanted you to do this, thank you!
いや、配信組は寂しいんじゃないのー？コメント見えてますよ！
No, aren't stream viewers lonely? I can see your comments!
ラグはあるけど、みんなが何を言うか予言しながら見るんで大丈夫！
There's lag, but I'll watch while guessing what you'll say, so it's fine!
あ！あぴぴ！あぴぴぴぴ！あぴぴ！
Ah! Apipi! Apipipipi! Apipi!
何かを受信したみたいだ、これは秘宝...
It seems like I received something, this is a treasure...
もーです！
Hello there!
YouTubeで放送している無料のチラみせ、ここまーでなっちゃうんだって。
The free preview broadcast on YouTube goes up to this point!
コメント見えてるんだけどさ、続きはねスポンサーで見られるらしいんだけど
I can see the comments, and apparently, you can watch the rest through the sponsor plan,
見に来てくんないかなー？ 見に来てくんない... ね、みんなもおねがいしてよ！
won't you come see it? Won't you come... Hey, everyone, please ask them too!
見に来てくんないかなー？
Won't you come watch it?
ワタメどもみんなもね、こう言ってるんだあのね、初めて見たって人もね
Watame and everyone else are saying this, you know—even if it's your first time seeing this,
ぜひ見てほしいなと思えます。
I really want you to check it out.
概要欄のねリンクからぜひ遊びに来てください！
Please be sure to come play via the link in the description!
え、それではワタメは一旦ねマイクを取りに行ってもいいですか？
Um, well then, would it be alright if Watame goes and grabs her mic for a moment?
いいよー！
Sure!
じゃあ、一旦マイクをねちょっと取りに行くので、みんなこの後も一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Alright, so I'm just going to go grab my mic real quick, so let's keep the hype going together afterwards too!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The free part has ended.
The free portion has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The free portion has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!